<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tag_a on JapanBonsai</title>
    <link>http://srilankasl.com/tags/tag_a/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tag_a on JapanBonsai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://srilankasl.com/tags/tag_a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Bonsai Masterpieces</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses1/</guid>
      <description>The Japan Bonsai of bonsai Art’s collection contains over 1000+ works of art from all cultures and time periods spanning 100 years of human creativity. The collection is dynamic; new acquisitions are being added all the time and the bonsai gallery are constantly changing. Below is a selection of highlights from the bonsai encyclopedic collection currently on view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BONSAI</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Bonsai (盆栽, &amp;ldquo;tray planting&amp;rdquo;) is a Japanese art form using trees grown in containers. Similar practices exist in other cultures, including the Chinese tradition of penjing from which the art originated. Japanese tradition dates back over a thousand years. &amp;ldquo;Bonsai&amp;rdquo; is a Japanese pronunciation of the earlier Chinese term penzai. The purposes of bonsai are primarily contemplation (for the viewer) and the pleasant exercise of effort and ingenuity (for the grower), by contrast with other plant cultivation practices, bonsai is not intended for production of food or for medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonsai Groth PRINCIPLES</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaigrouthprincipals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaigrouthprincipals/</guid>
      <description>This step-by-step pictorial is designed to guide beginners through the mechanical process of cutting, shaping and transplanting fairly simple bonsai material for the first time. It makes the assumption that the reader has already done some research and has a basic understanding of the fundamental shaping concepts used in the art of bonsai such as:
 Triangulation and asymmetrical composition. Primary, secondary and tertiary branch identification and placement. Selection of primary viewing angle based on trunk movement and rootage .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonsai Types</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaitypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaitypes/</guid>
      <description>Bonsai Styles It is important for you to remember, as a beginner, that no single bonsai style is the “right” style. Bonsai is meant to be a representation of a tree in nature. Crafting a bonsai masterpiece is tantamount to how YOU view that tree. You are not learning from a bonsai master, you are simply being given instruction on how to create your own bonsai. What you make of it lies simply in your own mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonsai Watering</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaiwatering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaiwatering/</guid>
      <description>More Bonsai die thru incorrect watering than any other cause, with the majority of those caused by “overwatering”. When the surface of the soil feels dry to the touch, water the plant until entire root ball is wet. DO NOT water again until the soil surface feels dry again. This can be as frequent as three times a day or as infrequent as every 3 days depending upon several conditions including time of year, plant health, and soil composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating A Bonsai For The First Time.</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/biginnerbasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/biginnerbasics/</guid>
      <description>This step-by-step pictorial is designed to guide beginners through the mechanical process of cutting, shaping and transplanting fairly simple bonsai material for the first time. It makes the assumption that the reader has already done some research and has a basic understanding of the fundamental shaping concepts used in the art of bonsai such as:
 Triangulation and asymmetrical composition. Primary, secondary and tertiary branch identification and placement. Selection of primary viewing angle based on trunk movement and rootage .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to grow your own Bonsai</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaigrowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaigrowing/</guid>
      <description>Buying a Bonsai tree in a shop is nice, but wouldn’t it be much better to do it yourself? A great way to start growing Bonsai trees is to buy a starterkit and style the tree into a Bonsai. A starterkit can be purchased at many (online) Bonsai shops, but you could also choose to buy only a young plant at a local gardencenter. This article explains the steps to grow a Bonsai tree from a starterkit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BONSAI SOIL</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaisoil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/bonsaisoil/</guid>
      <description>There are many different soil mixtures used to plant bonsai. Bonsai people in Florida, Scotland, Holland, Japan, Canada and California all have different growing conditions and different materials available to make soil mixtures. Most mixtures have one thing in common &amp;ndash; they don&amp;rsquo;t use garden soil. This is because shallow pots don&amp;rsquo;t drain as well as soil in the garden and as a result the roots can stay too wet and rot!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT MAKES GOOD BONSAI</title>
      <link>http://srilankasl.com/posts/whatmakesgoodbonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://srilankasl.com/posts/whatmakesgoodbonsai/</guid>
      <description>Signs of good health and stability such as leaf color and well settled, natural looking moss. No signs of carelessness and abuse such as badly healed pruning scars or scars from wire left on too long. A strong well shaped trunk springing naturally from the soil and moving upwards towards the apex in an even taper. A good fanning out of surface roots (nebari) from the base of the trunk gradually disappearing into the soil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
