<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>two on JapanBonsai</title>
    <link>https://srilankasl.com/categories/two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in two on JapanBonsai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:51:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://srilankasl.com/categories/two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Principles of Bonsai</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/principlesofbonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:51:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/principlesofbonsai/</guid>
      <description>Not all plants are equally effective as bonsai. To produce a realistic illusion of a mature tree, look for plants with the following characteristics:
  Small leaves or needles. Short internodes, or distances between leaves. Attractive bark or roots. Branching characteristics for good twig forms.  All parts of the ideal bonsai — trunk, branches, twigs, leaves, flowers, fruits, buds, roots — should be in perfect scale with the size of the tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pots And Culture Rules</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/potsandculturerules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/potsandculturerules/</guid>
      <description>Pots  The tree should be placed behind the mid line of the pot, and to the left or right of the center line. The depth of the pot should be the caliper of the trunk, except for cascades. Colored glazed pots should be used for flowering and fruiting trees and the colors should complement the flower color. The width of the pot should be 2/3 the height of the tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trunk and Nebari Rules</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/rulesofbonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/rulesofbonsai/</guid>
      <description>Height should be six times the caliper of the trunk. Trunk should lean slightly toward the viewer. Trunk should flare at base to visually anchor the plant. Roots should radiate from the flare. No eye-poking roots (directly at viewer). Apex should lean toward viewer. Trunk should taper as it ascends. No reverse taper. Grafts should match under stock and scion so that they are unobtrusive, or be    placed low enough to disappear into the nebari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules Of Branches</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/rulesofbranches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/rulesofbranches/</guid>
      <description>No crossing branches or branches that cross the trunk. No eye-poking branches (pointed directly at viewer). 3.First branch should be placed approximately 1/3 the height of the tree. Succeeding branches placed at 1/3 the remaining distance to the top of the tree. Branches go on the outside of the curves (No belly branches). Branch caliper should be in proportion to the trunk. Branches that are thicker than 1/3 the trunk caliper will be too thick.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
