<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Keto Diet For Me</title>
    <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Keto Diet For Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://srilankasl.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Keto diet</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/keto_diet_menu_for_the_week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/keto_diet_menu_for_the_week/</guid>
      <description>Monday  Breakfast: omelet with slices of bacon, tomato 🥗 Lunch: soup (chicken, broccoli, eggplant, sweet pepper) 🥗 Dinner: vegetable salad, a small piece of baked fish (preferably red).  Tuesday  Breakfast: unsweetened yogurt, nuts 🥗 Lunch: beef broth, egg, sauerkraut, a piece of meat 🥗 Dinner: stewed zucchini with chicken.  Wednesday  Breakfast: fried eggs, sweet peppers 🥗 Lunch: fish soup, but without potatoes, stewed green beans, chop 🥗 Dinner: tomatoes, cucumbers, chicken breast baked in fat sour cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to eat</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/what_to_eat_in_keto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/what_to_eat_in_keto/</guid>
      <description>Foods to be discarded:  Sugar and all kinds of sweets (marmalade, marshmallows, sweets, cake, ice cream). Cereals (wheat, rice, barley). Vegetable oil. (berries are allowed, in a minimum amount); Legumes (green bean pods are allowed); Root vegetables (beets, carrots, potatoes); Dietary options, for example, low-fat cottage cheese; Sauces, gravy containing starch, flour; Alcoholic drinks.  Ideal foods for diet:  Meat and all its types; Seafood, including fish; Eggs Vegetables containing a minimum of carbohydrates (bell pepper, eggplant, tomatoes); Dairy products (cheese, butter, fatty cottage cheese); Nuts Mushrooms; Oils (coconut, olive); Spices, spices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dish Recipes</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/dish_recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/dish_recipes/</guid>
      <description>Scrambled eggs with ham It is necessary to take:
 Egg 2 pcs. Ham 50 g Cream Cheese 50 g Olive oil 1 tbsp. Salt to taste Greens to taste   Fry the diced ham, beat in the eggs, and sprinkle with cheese on top. Fry no more than 3-4 minutes, add herbs and can be served.  Egg Omelet with Bacon  Egg2 pcs. Bacon2 slices Butter1 tbsp Cream100 g Salt to taste Red pepper to taste   Frying the bacon over high heat on both sides, we drive in the eggs, pepper, and salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefit for Health.</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/benefit_for_health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/benefit_for_health/</guid>
      <description>Based on the ketogenic diet, the well-being of people with obvious neurological problems improve. Practice shows that the number of symptoms of epilepsy, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s, and Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s has been reduced. This refers to effective methods of anti-cancer therapy. Because these cells feed on sugar, its significant reduction leads to the death of malignant cells. The condition of the skin improves, acne disappears. A decrease in insulin helps to get rid of chronic inflammation that affects the skin gradually.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
