<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tag_b on JapanBonsai</title>
    <link>https://srilankasl.com/tags/tag_b/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tag_b on JapanBonsai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://srilankasl.com/tags/tag_b/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to look after  my bonsai</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/how_to_carering_your_bonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/how_to_carering_your_bonsai/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to protecting a bonsai tree, watering, spraying, fertilizing the tree, and protecting our bonsai plant from seasonal changes, protection are just some of the things to keep in mind.
WATERING When? How often your Bonsai tree needs watering will depend on a number of different factors. Water your trees when the soil gets slightly dry. Use your fingers to check the soil at around one centimetre deep for dryness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Bonsai Masterpieces</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses1/</guid>
      <description>The Japan Bonsai of bonsai Art’s collection contains over 1000+ works of art from all cultures and time periods spanning 100 years of human creativity. The collection is dynamic; new acquisitions are being added all the time and the bonsai gallery are constantly changing. Below is a selection of highlights from the bonsai encyclopedic collection currently on view.
           All You Need To Know About Bonsai &amp;lsquo;How bonsai works&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important this to do become bonsai master</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/masterpieses2/</guid>
      <description>Important this to Do   choose suitable trees that adapt for local climatic conditions. Find the simple container with adequate drainage. Plant Tree in correct position in a container Do potting and re-potting at right time.    Carefully eliminate air pockets during potting and re-potting. Tree has to trim or prune regularly(Two month or decide its right time) to produce a fine network of shoots. Give good open air with sunlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BONSAI</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Bonsai (盆栽, &amp;ldquo;tray planting&amp;rdquo;) is a Japanese art form using trees grown in containers. Similar practices exist in other cultures, including the Chinese tradition of penjing from which the art originated. Japanese tradition dates back over a thousand years. &amp;ldquo;Bonsai&amp;rdquo; is a Japanese pronunciation of the earlier Chinese term penzai. The purposes of bonsai are primarily contemplation (for the viewer) and the pleasant exercise of effort and ingenuity (for the grower), by contrast with other plant cultivation practices, bonsai is not intended for production of food or for medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT MAKES GOOD BONSAI</title>
      <link>https://srilankasl.com/posts/whatmakesgoodbonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srilankasl.com/posts/whatmakesgoodbonsai/</guid>
      <description>Signs of good health and stability such as leaf color and well settled, natural looking moss. No signs of carelessness and abuse such as badly healed pruning scars or scars from wire left on too long. A strong well shaped trunk springing naturally from the soil and moving upwards towards the apex in an even taper. A good fanning out of surface roots (nebari) from the base of the trunk gradually disappearing into the soil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
